

Kiruba NIthy

Graphic Designer & VFX Artist

PROFILE

Dedicated & Hard working Graphic Designer & VFX With 10 Years Experince Who Loves To Pursue a Challenging Career That Provides Me Opportunities To Widen My Skills and To Apply Them Practically For The Overall Development Of The Concern I work For And Myself.

EDUCATION

B.SC VISUAL COMMUNICATION MANONMANIAM SUNDARANAR UNIVERSITY Aggregate of 65.8%. 2010-2013

EXPERTISE

Photoshop

Illustrator

Indesign

Premier Pro

FCP

After Effects

Canon DSLR



Video Camera —

PHONE +91 8217731735

EMAIL Knithy21@gmail.com

AREA Whitefield, Bangalore, Karnataka-560066

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer, VFX, Video Editing

2022-Present KHATIB & ALAMI / Bangalore

Graphic Designer, VFX, Video Editing

2021-2022 CHAITHANYA PROJECT PVT LTD / Bangalore

Graphic Designer, Motion Graphic, Video Editing

2019 - 2021 FOCALPLANE MEDIA / CChennai

Graphic Designer, Motion Graphic, Video Editing

017 - 2019 SPIRITUAL HIERARCHY PUBLICATION TRUST / Chennai

Graphic Designer, Video Editing

2016 - 2017 X STUDIOZ / Bangalore

2D VFX Instructor

2015 - 2016 AMAZE ANIMATION AND TECHNOLOGY / Pondicherry

Graphic Designer, Video Editing

2013 - 2015 X STUDIOZ / Pondicherry

LANGUAGE

English Tamil Hindi

PORTFOLIO LINK: https://www.behance.net/kirubanithy

INTERESTS









Travel Music Writing

Chess